/* grid with question on top and 4 answers, there should be a next/submit button and it should throw your score at the end ) */


let questions = [
  {
    question: "Illmatic 1994",
    a: "Biggie",
    b: "Jay Z",
    c: "Drake",
    d: "Nas",
    answer: "D"
  },

  {
    question: "My Beautiful Dark Twisted Fantasy (2010)",
    a: "Drake",
    b: "Frank Ocean",
    c: "Andre 3000",
    d: "Kanye West",
    answer: "d"
  },

  {
    question: "Get Rich or Die Tryin (2003)",
    a: "50 cent",
    b: "Jadakiss",
    c: "DMX",
    d: "Lloyd Banks",
    answer: "a",
  },

  {
    question: "Come Home with Me (2002)",
    a: "Juelz Santana",
    b: "Lil wayne",
    c: "Camron",
    d: "Eminem",
    answer: "c"
  },

  {
    question: "Tha Carter III (2008)",
    a: "50 Cent",
    b: "Eminem",
    c: "Lil Wayne",
    d: "Drake",
    answer: "C"
    
  },

  {
    question: "Blonde (2016)",
    a: "The Weeknd",
    b: "Frank Ocean",
    c: "Steve Lacy",
    d: "Tyler, The Creator",
    answer: "b"
    
  },

  {
    question: "Trilogy (2012)",
    a: "Frank Ocean",
    b: "Chris Brown",
    c: "The Weeknd",
    d: "Drake",
    answer: "c"
    
  },

  {
    question: "17 (2017)",
    a: "XXXTENTACION",
    b: "Kendrick lamar",
    c: "J.Cole",
    d: "Future",
    answer: "a"
    
  },

  {
    question: "The Life of Pablo (2016)",
    a: "Kid Cudi",
    b: "Travis Scott",
    c: "Kanye West",
    d: "Pablo Escobar",
    answer: "c"
    
  },

  {
    question: "Ready to Die (1994)",
    a: "2pac",
    b: "Biggie",
    c: "Big L",
    d: "Mase",
    answer: "b"
    
  }


];

function get(x) {
  return document.getElementById(x);
}


